<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecyclerView_Recipes</string>
    <string name="food">food</string>

    <string-array name="recipeNames">
        <item>Bacon &amp; Spinach Stuffed Chicken</item>
        <item>Tex-Mex Meatballs</item>
        <item>Best-Ever Calzones</item>
        <item>Baked Spaghetti</item>
        <item>Cheesy Ground Beef Tacos</item>
        <item>Beef Totchos</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="recipeDescriptions">
        <item>Hasselback your chicken by cutting shallow slits into your chicken breasts (don\'t cut all the way through!) and stuff each slit with bacon and a creamy spinach and artichoke filling. It will make your weeknight chicken dinner sing! </item>
        <item>Pro tip: These meatballs make a killer sub. Throw them on a hero roll with extra sauce and melt some cheddar on top.</item>
        <item>Calzones are seriously underrated. Seen as inferior to the grand pizza pie, calzones are often forgotten about, but why? They are basically an individual pizza all wrapped up. No cheese sliding off or floppy crusts. Just pure deliciousness wrapped up in a pillowy dough. Calzones deserve their chance to shine. </item>
        <item>Why make baked spaghetti instead of regular ol\' spaghetti with meat sauce? It\'s all about that melty layer of cheese on top! If you prefer, slice some fresh mozzarella to finish it off instead. </item>
        <item>Celebrate Taco Tuesday with these classic cheesy ground beef tacos. When a taco craving strikes, nothing else will do!</item>
        <item>Totchos or tater tot nachos are simply a twist on the classic nachos. The very well loved nachos never get boring, but just for kicks we took all of our favorite nacho toppings and placed them on top a bed of crispy tater tots. Be sure to cook the tater tots first so they have a chance to get crispy!</item>
    </string-array>
   <string-array name="recipeIngredients">
        <item>- 4 boneless skinless chicken breasts\n- Kosher salt\n- Freshly ground black pepper\n- 4 oz. cream cheese, softened\n- 1/2 c. frozen spinach, defrosted and drained\n- 1/3 c. chopped artichoke hearts\n- 1 c. shredded mozzarella, dividedPinch crushed red pepper flakes\n- 4 strips bacon, cut into 4 strips\n- 2 tbsp. extra-virgin olive oil </item>
        <item>1 1/2 lb. ground beef\n- 2 c. shredded Mexican cheese blend, divided\n- 1/2 c. panko bread crumbs\n- 2 tbsp. freshly chopped parsley, plus more for garnishn\2 cloves garlic, minced\n- 1 jalapeño, finely chopped\n- 1 large egg\n- 1 tsp. ground cumin\n- Kosher salt\n- Freshly ground black pepper\n- 1 tbsp. extra-virgin olive oil\n- 1/2 large onion, chopped\n- 1 (15-oz.) can crushed tomatoesn\n- 2 tbsp. chopped chipotle chiles in adobo sauce</item>
        <item>Cooking spray\n- 1 3/4 lb. pizza dough\n- All-purpose flour, for surface\n- 1 c. pizza sauce\n- 1 c. ricotta\n- 1/2 c. pepperoni\n- 1 c. shredded mozzarella\n- Extra-virgin olive oil, for brushing\n- Kosher salt</item>
        <item>Cooking spray\n- 16 oz. spaghetti\n- 2 tbsp. extra-virgin olive oil\n- 1 medium yellow onion, finely chopped\n- 2 cloves garlic, minced\n- 1 lb. ground beef\n- kosher salt\n- Freshly ground black pepper\n- 1 tsp. Italian seasoning\n- 1 (28-oz.) can crushed tomatoes\n- 1/2 c. basil, chopped\n- 1 c. shredded mozzarella\n- 1/4 c. freshly grated Parmesan\n- Chopped fresh parsley, for garnish</item>
        <item>1 large onion, chopped\n- 1 lb. ground beef\n- 1 (15-oz.) can fire-roasted tomatoes\n- 1 (15-oz.) can black beans, drained and rinsed\n- 1 tbsp. taco seasoning\n- kosher salt\n- 2 c. shredded cheddar or pepper jack\n- 8 Small flour tortillas\n- Sliced green onions, for serving\n- Sour cream, for serving</item>
        <item>Cooking spray\n- 2 (1-lb.) bags frozen tater tots\n- 1 tbsp. extra-virgin olive oil\n- 1 lb. ground beef\n- 1 tbsp. taco seasoning\n- 1 c. cherry tomatoes, quartered\n- 1 c. black beans\n- 1 jalapeño, sliced\n- 1 c. shredded cheddar\n- 1 c. shredded Monterey Jack\n- Sour cream, for serving\n- Guacamole, for serving\n- Freshly chopped cilantro, for serving</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="recipeProcedure">
        <item>1. Preheat oven to 400°. Line a large baking sheet with foil. Make slits widthwise in chicken, being careful not to cut all the way through chicken. Season with salt and pepper. Place on prepared baking sheet.\n2. In a medium bowl, combine cream cheese, spinach, artichokes, and ½ cup of mozzarella. Season with salt, pepper, and a pinch of red pepper flakes. Fill every other slit with cream cheese mixture and fill remaining slits with a piece of bacon. Sprinkle remaining ½ cup mozzarella on top and drizzle with oil.\n3. Bake until chicken is cooked through and bacon is crispy, 35 minutes.</item>
        <item>1. In a medium bowl, combine ground beef, 1 cup of cheese, bread crumbs, parsley, garlic, jalapeño, egg, and cumin and season with salt and pepper. Mix until combined, then form into meatballs.\n2. In a large skillet over medium-high heat, heat oil. Add meatballs in a single layer and sear 2 minutes per side. Transfer to a plate.\n3. Add onion to skillet and cook, stirring, until soft, 5 minutes. Stir in crushed tomatoes and chipotle in adobo and bring mixture to a boil. Reduce heat to medium-low and return meatballs to skillet. Cover and simmer until meatballs are cooked through, about 10 minutes.\n4. Top with remaining 1 cup cheese, then cover with lid to let melt, about 2 minutes.\n5. Garnish with parsley before serving.</item>
        <item>1. Preheat oven to 500° and grease two large baking sheets with cooking spray. Divide pizza dough into 4 pieces. On a lightly floured surface, roll one piece of dough out into an 8" circle, about ¼" thick. Spoon pizza sauce in middle of dough, then dot with ricotta and top with pepperoni and mozzarella.\n2. Gently fold dough in half, dampen seams with water and pinch together, then crimp edges all around. Repeat with remaining dough. Transfer to prepared baking sheets. Brush tops with oil and sprinkle with salt. Using kitchen scissors or a sharp knife, slit tops in 2 to 3 spots to create steam vents.\n3. Bake until tops are golden and filling is bubbling, 20 minutes, brushing with more oil halfway through. Let cool 5 minutes before cutting open.</item>
        <item>1. Preheat oven to 350°. Grease a medium baking dish with cooking spray. Cook spaghetti according to package directions until al dente, drain, and set aside.\n2. Meanwhile, in a large skillet over medium heat, heat oil. Add onions and cook until soft and translucent, about 5 minutes. Stir in garlic and cook until fragrant, 1 minute more. Add ground beef, season with salt, pepper, and Italian seasoning, and cook until no longer pink, about 8 minutes. Drain fat in a bowl lined with paper towels and return to pan. Pour in crushed tomatoes and basil and simmer until slightly reduced, about 10 minutes. Season with more salt and pepper to taste.\n3. Toss with spaghetti, then transfer to baking dish and top with mozzarella and Parmesan. Bake until cheese is melted and pasta is warmed through, about 20 minutes.\n4. Garnish with parsley and serve.</item>
        <item>1. In a large skillet over medium-high heat, cook onion until soft, 6 minutes. Add beef and cook until no longer pink, 5 to 7 minutes more, then add tomatoes, black beans, and taco seasoning and season with salt. Stir until combined. Add cheese and stir until completely melted.\n2. Spoon mixture into flour tortillas and fold. Garnish with green onions and serve with sour cream.</item>
        <item>1. Preheat oven to 450° and grease a 9”-x-13” baking dish with cooking spray. Add tater tots and bake until crispy, 20 minutes.\n2. In a large skillet over medium heat, heat oil. Add beef and cook until no longer pink, 6 minutes. Drain fat.\n3. Return skillet to stove and season with taco seasoning.\n4. Top tater tots with beef, tomatoes, black beans, jalapeños, and cheeses.\n5. Bake until warmed through and cheese is melty, 10 minutes.\n6. Top with sour cream, guacamole, and cilantro before serving.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>